collaboration communication and
coordination key to better project
management with clients and team thanks
to fluent boards front-end portal for
making these achievable more easily than
ever it allows you to access project
boards directly from the front end
without revealing backend operations
let's deal with clients and team
collaboration first to get this done you
can add them if they're already on your
WordPress site or invite them easily
using their email no matter where they
are an onboarding link will be sent in
seconds next manage member roles from
the settings to control what they can
access all right let's take a look at
the features and
modules spot the front end portal and
enable it from the settings right after
that you will get the flexibility to
Showcase your portal either via short
Cod or a dedicated page I'll choose a
standalone you URL because of its
Simplicity provide a URL slug as
suggested and save the changes in case
you already have a page simply select it
and add the short cat in it these easy
tasks wrap up the setup process now
let's see how it works on the front end
for that click the dedicated front end
portal button or the arrow voila the
sidebar disappears while everything else
stays the same
same no backend access no privacy
concerns but what happens when your
clients get this link let's check it out
as well all it takes to provide the
right credentials and they are on the
project
board and that's how FL and Boards not
only makes project management better but
also enhances engagement in every stage
so why wait grab FL boards now ad manage
any project better collaboratively with
clients and team members